dvdactive.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - Information - DVDActive

####  Privacy Statement

DVDActive have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for DVDActive.

####  Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to monitor traffic movement through our sites, your IP address isn't normally used to specifically identify you.

####  Cookies

DVDActive uses cookies to make sure you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly. Cookies may also be used by DVDActive as a means of remembering your DVD region, thereby not requiring you to click on your region on every visit. DVDActive uses cookies to make it easier for you to post messages and to help you keep track of messages that you have already viewed. Cookies may be used on the site as a means of tracking viewers in a non-specific manor to establish how users use our site.

####  Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.dvdactive.com/external.php?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.networkadvertising.org%2Fmanaging%2Fopt_out.asp).

In addition, this website may utilise certain services provided by DoubleClick, Inc. For further information concerning DoubleClick's privacy practices, including the ability to opt-out from any data collection, reporting and/or targeting activities associated with its services, please go [here](http://www.dvdactive.com/external.php?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.doubleclick.com%2Fus%2Fabout_doubleclick%2Fprivacy%2F).

####  Surveys

DVDActive's online surveys may ask visitors for demographic information (like postal code, age, or income level). This information will not be used to uniquely identify users. Instead, DVDActive uses this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our sites, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

####  External Links

DVDActive may contain links to other sites. DVDActive is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. For more information on this topic, please consult the disclaimer.

####  Special Relationships

DVDActive attempts to form relationships with other web sites, and such relationships can change regularly. If you would like more information, then contact us via email. Such relationships do not include the trading of user details.

####  Public Forums

DVDActive makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or commenting systems available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Similarly DVDActive cannot be held responsible for any information that is posted to these services, even though we may decide to remove it.

####  Security

DVDActive has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. All information stored about users is backed up regularly, and the information stored online is protected.

####  Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us. You can send an email to support@dvdactive.com or follow the details that are provided in the appropriate emails relating to unsubscribing.

####  Data Quality/Access

DVDActive gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: you can send email to [ support@dvdactive.com](mailto:support@dvdactive.com)

####  P3P

We provide P3P machine readable files to help your web browser make privacy related decisions automatically.

####  Dispute Resolution

Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative. Our customer service will promptly correct any errors.

####  Contacting DVDActive

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of DVDActive, or your dealings with DVDActive, then you can contact: [ support@dvdactive.com](mailto:support@dvdactive.com)
